<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>life on Skycloud</title>
    <link>https://skyly-night.github.io/skycloud/public/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in life on Skycloud</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://skyly-night.github.io/skycloud/public/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Future - What will it bring?</title>
      <link>https://skyly-night.github.io/skycloud/public/posts/003-future-what-will-it-bring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skyly-night.github.io/skycloud/public/posts/003-future-what-will-it-bring/</guid>
      <description>The interpretation of Earth as a ocean might feel a little weird at first, but there is so much truth in it. There may be storms in life, but just like a stormy weather it eventually passes. Together with other people it gets a lot easier to maneuver your little ship. There are thousands and millions of other ships, but every ship is unique. Every journey is unique. Every life is unique.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;The interpretation of Earth as a ocean might feel a little weird at first, but there is so much truth in it. There may be storms in life, but just like a stormy weather it eventually passes. Together with other people it gets a lot easier to maneuver your little ship. There are thousands and millions of other ships, but every ship is unique. Every journey is unique. Every life is unique. Isn&amp;rsquo;t it nice to think that way, everything about you is unique, and still you share specific details, like hobbies or interests, with others. That connects us with others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s be honest&amp;hellip; if life wasn&amp;rsquo;t difficult at some points, would it still be fun?
Would a roller coaster without any loops or sudden turns be fun;&amp;hellip; if it just went straight ahead, in a straight line, without any sudden or unpredictable twists? Would it be nice, to live a life, in which you could plan everything ahead. In which you know every twist, everything that might, or will ever happen. When there&amp;rsquo;s nothing unexpected anymore and you know the solution to every problem. When everything becomes predictable&amp;hellip;
I don&amp;rsquo;t think it would be just as nice, not as fun at least!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s face it; we cannot predict everything, we only know who we are, we don&amp;rsquo;t know who we will be. But now it the time to change, who you will be looking up back on, once you&amp;rsquo;re your future-self. Now is the time to shine, to change how people remember you, to change how you remember yourself. It might feel super overwhelming at some points in life, but that&amp;rsquo;s when you gotta push on. You&amp;rsquo;re not supposed to give up, you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to keep going, to show the world who you are and to show the world what you&amp;rsquo;re capable of! Those are the times when you need to prove that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The future inhabits so many mysteries, so much to find out, so many ways things can work out. You will never know what the end result of a journey will be, if you never try this specific journey. But keep in mind that it&amp;rsquo;s not always important to know exactly where you&amp;rsquo;re heading. You just need to start walking, and then you follow the paths automatically. You don&amp;rsquo;t know where exactly they&amp;rsquo;re going to lead you to, maybe it will turn out better than you&amp;rsquo;ve ever imagined. If you encounter failure or problems, you shall keep walking, the path will go on and bring you somewhere eventually.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You as a person have the ability to decide every single day. There are so many decisions that we make, so many trails we chose to walk. Probably every time we&amp;rsquo;re making a decision, we&amp;rsquo;re choosing to take a different track. A unique track, that will lead you to a completely different place, a completely different journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes there also may be tracks that lead you back on the original path it came from. You have a little workaround, which may have been even prettier, than the path you&amp;rsquo;ve came from. Or perhaps it may be a shortcut, which gives you a jump ahead, even if it was a little harder to walk through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your very own journey is unique. It belongs to no one else but you! You&amp;rsquo;re the person who walked this journey, you&amp;rsquo;re the one who will continue it, and you&amp;rsquo;re the person who will be looking back on the whole journey. Thinking about how it was, what maybe could have been so different, or who will be able to identify the key decisions of your journey!
The most exciting part- you won&amp;rsquo;t know, just until you&amp;rsquo;ve walked your unique path!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
