<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Skycloud</title>
    <link>https://skyly-night.github.io/skycloud/public/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Skycloud</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://skyly-night.github.io/skycloud/public/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Future - What will it bring?</title>
      <link>https://skyly-night.github.io/skycloud/public/posts/003-future-what-will-it-bring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skyly-night.github.io/skycloud/public/posts/003-future-what-will-it-bring/</guid>
      <description>The interpretation of Earth as a ocean might feel a little weird at first, but there is so much truth in it. There may be storms in life, but just like a stormy weather it eventually passes. Together with other people it gets a lot easier to maneuver your little ship. There are thousands and millions of other ships, but every ship is unique. Every journey is unique. Every life is unique.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;The interpretation of Earth as a ocean might feel a little weird at first, but there is so much truth in it. There may be storms in life, but just like a stormy weather it eventually passes. Together with other people it gets a lot easier to maneuver your little ship. There are thousands and millions of other ships, but every ship is unique. Every journey is unique. Every life is unique. Isn&amp;rsquo;t it nice to think that way, everything about you is unique, and still you share specific details, like hobbies or interests, with others. That connects us with others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s be honest&amp;hellip; if life wasn&amp;rsquo;t difficult at some points, would it still be fun?
Would a roller coaster without any loops or sudden turns be fun;&amp;hellip; if it just went straight ahead, in a straight line, without any sudden or unpredictable twists? Would it be nice, to live a life, in which you could plan everything ahead. In which you know every twist, everything that might, or will ever happen. When there&amp;rsquo;s nothing unexpected anymore and you know the solution to every problem. When everything becomes predictable&amp;hellip;
I don&amp;rsquo;t think it would be just as nice, not as fun at least!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s face it; we cannot predict everything, we only know who we are, we don&amp;rsquo;t know who we will be. But now it the time to change, who you will be looking up back on, once you&amp;rsquo;re your future-self. Now is the time to shine, to change how people remember you, to change how you remember yourself. It might feel super overwhelming at some points in life, but that&amp;rsquo;s when you gotta push on. You&amp;rsquo;re not supposed to give up, you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to keep going, to show the world who you are and to show the world what you&amp;rsquo;re capable of! Those are the times when you need to prove that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The future inhabits so many mysteries, so much to find out, so many ways things can work out. You will never know what the end result of a journey will be, if you never try this specific journey. But keep in mind that it&amp;rsquo;s not always important to know exactly where you&amp;rsquo;re heading. You just need to start walking, and then you follow the paths automatically. You don&amp;rsquo;t know where exactly they&amp;rsquo;re going to lead you to, maybe it will turn out better than you&amp;rsquo;ve ever imagined. If you encounter failure or problems, you shall keep walking, the path will go on and bring you somewhere eventually.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You as a person have the ability to decide every single day. There are so many decisions that we make, so many trails we chose to walk. Probably every time we&amp;rsquo;re making a decision, we&amp;rsquo;re choosing to take a different track. A unique track, that will lead you to a completely different place, a completely different journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes there also may be tracks that lead you back on the original path it came from. You have a little workaround, which may have been even prettier, than the path you&amp;rsquo;ve came from. Or perhaps it may be a shortcut, which gives you a jump ahead, even if it was a little harder to walk through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your very own journey is unique. It belongs to no one else but you! You&amp;rsquo;re the person who walked this journey, you&amp;rsquo;re the one who will continue it, and you&amp;rsquo;re the person who will be looking back on the whole journey. Thinking about how it was, what maybe could have been so different, or who will be able to identify the key decisions of your journey!
The most exciting part- you won&amp;rsquo;t know, just until you&amp;rsquo;ve walked your unique path!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The world and everything in it</title>
      <link>https://skyly-night.github.io/skycloud/public/posts/002-the-world-and-everything-in-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skyly-night.github.io/skycloud/public/posts/002-the-world-and-everything-in-it/</guid>
      <description>For me it&amp;rsquo;s just soo magical that pretty much every technology we use today, was invented just a few decades ago. The world must have been so different back then. Radio technology was introduced about 100 years ago, and nowadays we just take it for granted. Not only that, but we even start to use it less and less, because the internet has advanced this much.
I&amp;rsquo;m wondering how radio works to be honest, how was any human even able to invent this.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;For me it&amp;rsquo;s just soo magical that pretty much every technology we use today, was invented just a few decades ago. The world must have been so different back then. Radio technology was introduced about 100 years ago, and nowadays we just take it for granted. Not only that, but we even start to use it less and less, because the internet has advanced this much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m wondering how radio works to be honest, how was any human even able to invent this. Sure&amp;hellip;it wasn&amp;rsquo;t just there, but it was a really long process to get there, but how did we do that! And we keep developing so quickly! Can anyone relate to how I feel??&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soo since I don&amp;rsquo;t know what to add to this- I might just talk about what I often do:
I absolutely love to look at the night sky. When the sky is clear and the lights around you are not too bright, and you can look soo far into the universe. I fell in love with the view, and I love to think about how many other people look at the same stars as I&amp;rsquo;m looking at, in the same moment as I&amp;rsquo;m looking at them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know this sounds obvious, but have you ever thought about the fact that we all look at the same moon everyday. Every human has seen the moon at some point in their lives, and that gives me a feeling of connectivity. It makes me somewhat proud and happy to feel so connected with every other human. Those evening, when I look at the night sky, are exactly the evening when I feel so much hope. I think about how much there is out there, ready for us to explore. I&amp;rsquo;m not even talking about the universe, I&amp;rsquo;m talking about planet Earth itself.
You can totally spent a lifetime exploring every place the moonshine is hitting right now, and even then you will only have seen a small portion of the world, and you only stayed on this lovely planet. You haven&amp;rsquo;t been to our closest neighbor Mars, or any other planet in our solar-system. Not only that, you weren&amp;rsquo;t even close to leaving the solar-system, and there has to be so much more in our galaxy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To sum it up, there is a lot to explore, and we can still learn new things every day. We can write our own stories, we write our life stories and we created memories everyday! Don&amp;rsquo;t you think that&amp;rsquo;s just so awesome! We have the ability to decide. We can decide what we want to do, how we treat others, how we view the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would love to hear what you think about that! So go ahead, tell me!! Make a request on GitHub!!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my blog!</title>
      <link>https://skyly-night.github.io/skycloud/public/posts/001-welcome-to-my-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skyly-night.github.io/skycloud/public/posts/001-welcome-to-my-blog/</guid>
      <description>Hey, welcome to this lovely little blog. In this blog I&amp;rsquo;m going to share my thoughts on certain things with you guys! I think that the blog will be somewhat Philosophical, and that I can work things out together with people from all around the world. I generally think that this is just soo insane about the internet, I know most people feel like this is normal nowadays, but I&amp;rsquo;m still fascinated like a little kid by the fact that people from far overseas can read this blog&amp;hellip;in a matter of seconds!</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Hey, welcome to this lovely little blog. In this blog I&amp;rsquo;m going to share my thoughts on certain things with you guys! I think that the blog will be somewhat Philosophical, and that I can work things out together with people from all around the world.
I generally think that this is just soo insane about the internet, I know most people feel like this is normal nowadays, but I&amp;rsquo;m still fascinated like a little kid by the fact that people from far overseas can read this blog&amp;hellip;in a matter of seconds!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For me this is just such a absurd thing, I can&amp;rsquo;t imagine how all of this works, especially without any major failures. Anyway, back to the topic&amp;hellip; Soo as you might already have noticed I&amp;rsquo;m fascinated like a little kid, that&amp;rsquo;s exploring the world and let me tell you, we all should be! I think that every human is a kid of the universe, and we&amp;rsquo;re here to explore it, to some extend at least. We&amp;rsquo;re so small compared to literally everything, but still we are being a part of it! We&amp;rsquo;re being a part of the universe and that is my favorite way to think about the universe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our time is very limited, but we can use the time we have. The most important thing for me is to make the world just a little nicer for other people. We as humans should be a community after all, despite all the differences we have, we&amp;rsquo;re all human after all, we&amp;rsquo;re all kids of the universe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soo I assume now you really see in which direction this blog is going. I hope you enjoy it!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
